98 Duxbury Rd Hatfield, Pretoria Gauteng, 0083

30th August 2021

To whom it may concern...

I am currently Studying BEng Mechanical Engineering, in my final year of study at the University of Pretoria. Among others here is a few attributes that make me useful in the workspace. Firstly, my experience with working with people includes: I have worked with first year students in years 2017 and 2018 under the University of Pretoria's Education and Innovation Staff. I am a General Committee member for the Ubuntu Box Initiative. My work experience with admin includes the following: 2018 I did data capturing for the Education and Innovation orientation. I am a 2IC at CRC church, so I am fluent with taking registers and keeping track of time and organising in general. My work experience with working in a team includes: Ubuntu Box General Committee requires a lot of group work organising events and other student related issues. 2019 and 2020 I had the privilege of overlooking the orientation on main campus under Education and Innovation Department.

I am a multiskilled individual with a natural ability to understand, adapt and work efficiently. My most attractive attributes include a solid work ethic and ability not to buckle under pressure. I am really excited by the opportunity to work for you. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely

Ntuthuko Siphamandla Rich Sibiya

Ntuthukorich@gmail.com

0814586952 - Phone No.

Career Objective

I am an eager Mechanical engineering student who believes there is a machine that can solve any and every problem. I pride myself in overcoming challenges and keeping a consistent work ethic, in projects given to me.

Personal Information

Name : Ntuthuko Siphamandla Rich Sibiya

Surname : Sibiya

Date of Birth : 16 May 1998

Identity number : 9805165514087

Tax Number : 2100991179

Nationality : South African

Home Address : Mvunyane Sofaya Area Mondlo 3100

Contact Details : 0814586952

Email Address : ntuthukorich@gmail.com

Educational Background

2017 (current) <u>Undergraduate studies in Mechanical Engineering</u>

University of Pretoria

Major in: Structural Design

Project Management

Programming

2014-2016 National Senior Certificate, Star College Durban

Subjects: 6 distinctions in Mathematics, Engineering Graphics and Design,

Zulu, Geography, Life Science, Life Orientation

2012-2014 High School: Holy Family College.

Skills Summary

- SolidWorks and Or CAD competence
- Python programming competence
- Leadership Skills: Soft and Hard
- Advanced Microsoft office
- Libre Office competent
- Public Speaking: Prepared and Unprepared
- Works well in teams Outstanding Planning

Training

2017 Short course in Workshop

- Welding: Arc, MIG
- Soldering
- Panel Wiring
- Machining and Milling

2019 Mentorship Training

• People skills: Motivating, overseeing, monitoring and general assistance.

2019 Basic IT Maintenance

• University of Pretoria IT department.

2021 Huawei 5G

5G Fundamental Training

Achievements

- Head of Education and Innovation Orientation
- Glory Home Cell's 2IC
- Residence Master
- PTS Project Manager for Charity Projects

Employment History

2018-2018 <u>University of Pretoria</u>

Data Capturing

■ Laptop Runner during Orientation

2018-2018 <u>Star College Pretoria</u>

Part time tutor for Mathematics and Physical Science

Extracurricular Interests

Tutoring and Mentoring the underprivileged students

Researching on the latest technological Advances

Financial Market Analyst

Church and Serving

Hobbies: Basketball, Swimming and Chess

References

Prof Ana Naidoo, Deputy Director Department of Education and Innovation

Cell: 082 786 9313 Tel: 012 420 3323

Email: ana.naidoo@up.ac.za

Ms Hlengiwe P. Sehlapelo, Senior Researcher University of Pretoria, Department for Education Innovation

IT Building 3-38.5

Pretoria 0001

Cell: +27 82 378 8819 Tel: 012 420 3884